<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eunjae&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kckjn97.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eunjae&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 11:33:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kckjn97.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 11:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/project/</guid>
      <description>Project  목차  연구 (IO최적화) 관련  SAGE: 확률 그래프 분석 프레임워크 설계 및 IO 최적화 연구 클라우드 환경을 위한 Persistent Memory 캐시 연구 차세대 NVMe 요소 기술 연구 디스크 기반 그래프엔진에서의 IO 최적화 및 캐시 기법 연구 멀티테넌트 환경에서 IO 비율을 조절하기 위한 스케쥴링 기법 연구 LeavO 캐시: SSD Cache와 HDD RAID5로 이루어진 하이브리드 스토리지에서의 캐시 기법 연구 DM-SRC: Log-Structured RAID 기반의 대용량 SSD Array 캐시 기법 연구 SSD의 FTL에서의 Extent Mapping 기법 연구 eSAP: 플래시의 신뢰도와 성능 향상을 위한 Chip-level RAID5 기법 연구   웹 / 백엔드 서버 개발 관련  가상화폐 커밋로그 모니터링 시스템 트위터 이벤트 실시간 랜딩페이지 워드프레스 기반 쇼핑몰 개발 오픈마켓 상품 모니터링 시스템 잇츠뷰: 체험형 블로그 리뷰 웹서비스 ErrClipse: 디버깅 기록을 위한 Eclipse 플러그인</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications &amp; Patents</title>
      <link>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/publications-patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 01:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/publications-patents/</guid>
      <description>Publications &amp;amp; Patents By First Author  (Under Review) Uncertain Graph Analysis System, 2021 &amp;ldquo;Pre-select static caching and neighborhood ordering for bfs-like algorithms on disk-based graph engines&amp;rdquo;, Eunjae Lee, Junghyn Kim, Keunhak Lim, Sam H. Noh, Jiwon Seo, USENIX Annual Technical Conference (ATC), 2019 [more] &amp;ldquo;SSD caching to overcome small write problem of disk-based RAID in enterprise environments&amp;rdquo;, Eunjae Lee, Yongseok Oh, and Donghee Lee, The 30th ACM/SIGAPP Symposium On Applied Computing (SAC), 2015 [more] &amp;ldquo;LeavO Cache: SSD cache overcomming small write problem of RAID by keeping old data&amp;rdquo;, Eunjae Lee, Yongseok Oh, Jongmoo Choi, Donghee Lee, and Sam H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 05:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Portfolio  Publication &amp;amp; Patent Project Github  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 05:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kckjn97.github.io/posts/profile/</guid>
      <description>Profile Eunjae Lee (이은재)  UNIST Ph.D candidate (2021.08) Software Developer / Computer Science Researcher Email: kckjn97@gmail.com Github: github.com/kckjn97 Project Publication &amp;amp; Patent  Research Interests  Graph processing system Storage Distributed system Web development  Technical Skills  Programming Language  Major  C/C++, Python   Minor  Java, Javascript, Go, PHP, Bash     Experienced Library / Framework  Linux Kernel (Device-Mapper, Software RAID, NVMeDriver, VFS) Boost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
